#### http://morningharwood.com matthhar12@gmail.com 415.483.6018

# Matthew Harwood

# Developer + Multidisciplinary Designer

I am a generalist; slowly becoming a specialist in Web Development. I mix art, design, and technology, to create effective experiences that deliver value at scale. My professional goals are simple: surround myself by smart, energetic, creative people while working on solving problems that matter.

# Experience

#### R/GA @ Google Mountain View

August 2015 ~ Present Senior Software Engineer

Works as an embedded Software Engineer for Google's Interactive Marketing Division.

#### AKQA S.F.

January 2014 ~ August 2015 Creative Developer

Worked as a Designer and Developer for physical and digital brand experiences e.g. Target and Nike. Also, worked as an embedded Web Developer for Apple's Interactive Marcom division.

#### **QOMO HiteVision**

January 2010 ~ January 2012 Marketing Developer

Created comprehensive marketing materials through web, print, and video for businesses, educational, and governmental establishments.

# Education

#### **Simon Fraser University**

September 2011 ~ January 2014 B.S. Interactive Systems

Studied how to design, develop, and apply interactive systems with particular emphasis on how people use them through a combination of computing foundations, user-centred design principles, and programming practice.

## **Wayne State University**

September 2005 ~ January 2008 B.A. Asian Studies

To prepare students for the increasing demand for professionals with training in Chinese and Japanese.

## **Oakland Community College**

January 2004 ~ December 2005 Liberal Arts Associate's Degree

September 2008 ~ December 2010 Software Engineering Associate's Degree

# **Technical**

Object Oriented JavaScript, AngularJS, AWS, CSS/SCSS, Vector/DOM motion graphics, semantic HTML, Typescript, NodeJS, Golang, and a strong emphasis on i18n, a11y, and web workflow.

## **Interests**

Interaction Design, Fullstack Development, ES6, CSS, Modern Web Workflow, Angular 2, Industrial Design, Typography, Entrepreneurship, Motion Design, Architecture, Skateboarding, and Guitar.

# Social

GitHub matthewharwood LinkedIn morningharwood

Facebook watashi
Twitter matty0187

Google+ +matthewHarwood